{
    "id": "6c67f8bc4fe74e308bc37f8d8ca5ba88",
    "title": "Too And Enough",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "There were ……………….. many questions to answer so I ran out of time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "b0a3a28834514351b3124b6f4568daff"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is old ………………… to make her own bed now.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "enough",
                "too"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "7c637d7e8224422abd15f7d1ca3f5897"
        },
        {
            "question": "The tea was ………………….. hot for me to drink.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "453cdf1beaff49069f9c72f059177940"
        },
        {
            "question": "The room was …………………. so I turned the heating off.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "too enough",
                "hot enough"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "15b7ad8f089244b99b5b5eab61e2ffd0"
        },
        {
            "question": "I didn’t buy the laptop because it was …………………",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "enough expensive",
                "too expensive"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "dde6b272236a40d990762a05f38e33cf"
        },
        {
            "question": "The shirt was ………………. so I didn’t buy it.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "too small",
                "small enough"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "59971645f9ee4d43ad82bbf65cc3a714"
        },
        {
            "question": "The tablet is ……………… to fit inside your pocket.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "too small",
                "small enough"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c8f5e62a4e7944fdbee8a2f20436aa59"
        },
        {
            "question": "It is ………………. to start a new lesson now.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "too late",
                "late enough"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8de684e0b84c485f9ff338dc7e84d22c"
        },
        {
            "question": "I haven’t got …………………. to buy the tickets.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "too money",
                "enough money"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "52b00aa86071465b9c97043a7705e89a"
        },
        {
            "question": "It was ……………… to carry.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "too light",
                "light enough"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1d3f3e4eba864a709e202b84ef88c462"
        }
    ]
}